[Music]
[Música]
Marta, can I ask you what you think about
Marta te puedo preguntar qué te parece
Ana Rosa changing to the mornings? Or
el cambio a las mañanas de Ana Rosa O
would you rather not answer? I don't care. It
prefieres no contestar no me da igual me
seems to me that she has failed in the afternoon and is
parece que ha fracasado en la tarde y
returning to the place that she considers to be
vuelve al lugar que ella considera que
safe. Well, because you think what do you understand
es seguro bueno por cre tú qué entiendes
about television? I really find an
de tele encuentro en realidad una
explanation because, let's see if Ana Rosa
explicación porque vamos ver si Ana Rosa
already had. I mean, if she has been there for so many years, I
ya ya tenía O sea si lleva tantos años
understand in the morning because she was doing very
entiendo en la mañana porque le iba muy
well. I mean, why did she move to the afternoon?
bien o sea Por qué al pasarse a la tarde
Not to see because I think that
no a ver porque yo creo que el programa
Ana Rosa's afternoon program is a
de Ana Rosa por la tarde es un [__]
real pain, you know,
realmente sabes
and I don't like the collaborators at all. I do
y los colaboradores no me gustan nada
n't like the topics at all. And I think that
los temas no me gustan nada y creo que
to be on in the afternoon she should have
para estar en la tarde debería haber
done more fresh content. I
hecho un contenido como más fresco Me
find it tacky, you know, and
resulta casposo sabes y
in the morning she was doing well because that
que en la mañana le iba bien porque esa
current affairs is how things happen at the
actualidad es como pasan las cosas en el
moment, the events, the politics, but
momento los sucesos la política tal pero
in the afternoon, it's like the chip she had, you
ya por la tarde como que el chip tenía
know, to
tienes que cambiarlo sabes como para
entertain and I think that Ana Rosa hasn't
entretener y creo que Ana Rosa en eso no
done well in that, from my point of
no lo ha hecho bien bajo mi punto de
view as a viewer, you know, but it's not
vista de telespectador sabes pero no
only Ana Rosa that's It's that there is no
solamente Ana Rosa es Es que tampoco hay
innovation either. There is no  newness is
una Innovación No hay ninguna novedad es
all very monotonous it's all very very worthy
todo muy monótono es todo muy muy digno
to take a nap I mean it's like there's
para echar la siesta o sea es como no
nothing that moves you they give you
hay hay nada que te conmueva que te den
gas that's what they call it siest tear which I
gas así lo llaman siest tear que me
love the name siest tear I didn't know
encanta el nombre siest tear no sabía
it's but it's like the audience in
sea pero es como que el público de por
the afternoon is different than the one in
la de por la tarde es otro que el de por
the morning no because of course I mean look at me
la mañana no porque claro o sea mira yo
one thing that I always have with the issue
una cosa que tengo siempre con el tema
of audiences of of as if we were I
de las audiencias de de ni que fuéramos
say man how will they be watching the
digo tío cómo estarán viendo las
audiences I'm telling you sincerely it's not
audiencias te lo digo sinceramente no es
normal I don't believe in that I do
normal Yo es que en eso no creo yo es
n't believe in that Mar it's not normal the
que en eso no creo Mar no es normal la
viralization of the videos people on
viralización de los vídeos la gente por
the street how they stop us but when I
la calle cómo nos para pero cuando te
tell you when they stop me they don't stop me like
digo cuando me paran no me paran en plan
Oh Marta I love it it's not Marta What a
de Ay Marta me encanta no es Marta Qué
laugh with a jerk I don't know what no and I think it's
risa con patón no sé qué no y yo pienso
impossible that they made a
es que es imposible que hayan hecho un
two it's impossible It's that I don't
dos es imposible Es que yo eso no lo
believe that because it's that it's not It's that that's
creo porque es que eso no es Es que eso
an estimate that's not I mean the
es una estimación eso no es o sea yo los
real numbers are here on the internet not
números reales son aquí en internet no
the likes the viewers and all that that
los likes los espectadores y todo eso
is accounted for but the thing about the
eso sí está contabilizado pero lo de la
Tele is like a barometer based on the
tele es como un barómetro en base a la
machine, no, and I don't
maquinita no y yo es que eso no me lo
believe that 100% the truth is, I think
creo al 100% la verd yo creo que está ya
the whole issue of audiences is already, I think it
todo el tema de las audiencias creo que
's like outdated and all that. And for example,
está como desfasado y tal Y por ejemplo
in Ten, I think that in Ten it is that you cannot
en ten creo que en ten es que no se
measure it in Ten, it is that it is impossible, I mean, I could
puede medir en ten es que es imposible o
n't give myself the audience of
sea es que no pu me di la audiencia de
Ten and Marta. Do you think that if? Eh, in the end it
ten y Marta Tú crees que si Eh Al final
ends up on Spanish television, how
terminase en televisión española como
are the rumors that if you know something, I
son los rumores que si sabes algo
understand that you cannot tell me here,
entiendo que no me lo puedes contar aquí
but you are going to tell me tomorrow by
pero me lo vas a contar mañana por
phone. Do you think that they would censor
teléfono Tú crees que os censurarían
the content a lot? I mean, it could not
mucho el contenido O sea ya no podría
be the same content as it is
ser el mismo contenido igual que es
now, and let's say with Salvame, don't even think about it,
ahora y vamos el de salvame ni pensarlo
no, I think, let's see from what I'm watching,
no yo creo a ver por lo que estoy viendo
La Uno, La Uno. It seems to me that it is
la uno la uno Me parece que lo está
doing incredibly because it is, let's say,
haciendo increíble porque está vamos
some programs that I would not think of
unos programas que yo tampoco pensaría
before, for example with Broncano, eh, they
antes por ejemplo con broncano eh que se
make certain jokes, certain
hacen ciertos ciertas bromas ciertos
jokes that I about drugs, I don't know what, about
chistes que yo de drogas de no sé qué de
the facts that I would never
los fatos que yo eso antes no lo
think about before, I don't think that even if we were
pensaría jamás creo que ni que fuéramos
that you flip out on
tiene una cabida que flipas en la en
Spanish television now I don't know
televisión española ahora no sé
obviously there are things that I think
obviamente hay cosas que creo que no se
couldn't be done especially certain fights
podrían hacer sobre todo ciertas broncas
and certain things that have happened I think that
y ciertas cosas que han pasado creo que
one can't happen but for
la uno no pueden ocurrir pero por
example what happened with you, for example the
ejemplo lo de te p un ejemplo el
program on Friday, the thing with the patón because of
programa del viernes lo de patón por
these as they called it
estos como lo llamaron
in television hooliganism you know do you believe in
en gamberrismo televisivo sabes tú crees
Spanish television a scene I mean that it
en televisión española una escena O sea
's healthy and it's very it's not that there's anything
que que es sano y es muy no se trata que
wrong with it but no wow Do you think that
tenga de malo pero no buf Tú crees que
could be broadcast on
eso se podría emitir en televisión
Spanish television like that [ __ ]
España así [__]
pu the riots fun all day
pu las revueltas cachondeo todos día
too but at 6 in the afternoon Yeah but I don't
tambén pero las 6 de la tarde Sí pero no
know but not for any reason but because if for me, I mean it's that it's
sé pero no por nada sino porque si a mí
hard for me to watch it on
o sea que es que me cuesta verlo en
Spanish television but not because I'm we
televisión española pero no porque esty
're not used to it you know at 6 in
estamos desacostumbrado sabes a las 6 de
the t for me You know what happens to me for
la t a mí Sabes qué me pasa que a mí por
example it was hard for me to watch on
ejemplo me costaba ver en televisión
Spanish television many things that I'm seeing
española muchas cosas que estoy viendo
now
ahora
and I mean now I see Margo doing
y o sea yo ahora veo a Margo haciendo
some jokes like this opens a Cano the same and
unos vaciles de tal abre un Cano igual y
I think wow this was unthinkable
yo pienso ostras esto era impensable
two years ago yeah totally I think it's
hace dos años sí total Yo creo que es
getting used to it is getting used to it man
acostumbrarse es acostumbrarse hombre
with José Pablo and such that the floodgates are opening up a bit yes yes yes
con José Pablo y tal que se abre un poco
yes man obviously
la veda sí sí sí sí hombre evidentemente
like salvam men and we talk and I imagine that
como salvam men y hablamos y imagino que
in the case that
en el caso de que de que se vaya
Spanish television leaves maybe we have to
televisión española igual hay que
adapt a little it is not what
adaptarse un poquito no es lo que dices
you say that there are certain arguments that even if we
tú que hay ciertas broncas que aunque ni
weren't there the content has been lowered
que fuéramos haya rebajado el contenido
a bit the tone etc. Maybe we have to
un poco el tono etc A lo mejor hay que
adapt a little without losing the
amoldarse un poquito no sin quitar la
identity I think that precisely now the
identidad creo que precisamente ahora el
atmosphere that is breathed and that we were there
ambiente que se respira y que fuéramos
is more humor than tension you know yes I
es más humor que crispación sabes s yo
think that is the path a bit of
creo que ese es el camino un poco de de
Spanish television the one that I think
televisión española el que creo que nos
could take us I don't know to
podría llevar No lo sé a televisión
Spanish television the one of humor I think has been
española el del humor yo creo que se ha
right Also because the tension
acertado Además porque la crispación
precisely in these moments that we are
justamente en estos momentos que
going through already at a level with society
atravesamos ya a nivel con la sociedad
with how the panorama is with the
con como está el panorama con las
increases in everything cont tar is what is least
subidas de todo cont tar es lo que menos
needed you know that before it worked
falta hace sabes que antes funcionaba
very well Yes of course and and that
muy bien el Sí claro y y que ha cambiado
the issue has changed a lot when it comes to criticizing
mucho el tema de a la hora de criticar a
the characters such it changes it has
los personajes tal se cambia se ha
changed a lot from when it was sálvame or
cambiado mucho a cuando era sálvame o
when I was in Ana Rosa
cuando estaba yo en Ana Rosa se se ha
the way of making television has changed completely, I
cambiado totalmente la forma de de hacer
mean now there's no more
televisión o sea ahora ya no se hace
blood, before there was blood before it was like everyone
sangre antes hacía sangre antes es que
went all out for someone, Piñón now it's
se iba a piñon por alguien a Piñón ahora
done but more from laughter, from
se va pero más desde la risa desde el
humor, it's much more respected, eh the
humor más se se respeta mucho más eh
whole topic for example of Mental Health is
todo el tema ejemplo de Salud Mental se
highly respected You know that before it was
respeta muchísimo Sabes eso antes era
absurd and now right away there are like some
absurdo y ahora enseguida hay como unas
lines that are not crossed that
líneas que no se sobrepasan que
right away it's like everyone is
enseguida es como que todos están
learning and we are learning Yeah,
aprendiendo y estamos aprendiendo Si
look what Patón has managed to do without
fíjate que patón ha conseguido sin sin
him wanting it in part thanks to you eh
él quererlo en parte Gracias a ti eh
make half of Spain dislike him to fall to
caerle mal a media España a caer a que
us to like us you know I mean, look
nos caiga bien sabes o sea yo Es que
Alejandro is just telling him I
mira justo le está diciendo Alejandro
just saw the name of
digo Acabo de ver cómo se llama el
tomorrow's program that I'm going to go on tomorrow and it's
programa de mañana que voy mañana y es
what Patón and Agata did on Monday
lo heicho paton y agata de lunes
so I can already imagine that if I don't
entonces ya me puedo imaginar que si no
go to the
voy mañana al
office tomorrow tomorrow I think you're going to dance
despacho mañana creo que vas a bailar
tomorrow on the bus eh I think again
mañana en el autobús eh yo creo otra vez
my goodness well yeah I hope not on the
madre mía bueno ya Espero que en el
bus now that it's my turn that's the
autobús no a a ver ahora que me toca es
good thing about my fame is that you
que es lo bueno de ni que famos es que
don't really know  you don't know what you're going for I
no sabes realmente no sabes a qué vas te
swear Javi It's that you don't know what you're going for, I mean
lo juro Javi Es que no sabes a qué vas o
I get up and they tell me we'll
sea yo me levanto y me dicen te
pick you up at 2:10 okay And I get
recogemos a las 210 tal vale Y yo llego
there suddenly they say spies in the meeting
allí de repente dice espas en la reunión
eh Marta look eh There I don't know what And you're going to
eh Marta mira eh Hay no sé qué Y te vas
such But you don't know I mean you
a tal Pero tú no lo sabes o sea no te
can't prepare anything or anything no nothing nothing
puedes preparar nada ni nada no nada
zero it's that those are the true
nada cero es que esos son los verdaderos
creators of content eh I mean nothing
creadores de contenido eh o sea de nada
because the truth is that Agatha's thing did
porque en verdad es que lo de Agatha
n't give anything more I mean she already
tampoco daba para más O sea ya se
apologized even I think not the comment and
disculpó incluso creo no el comentario y
not the Agatha thing Agatha has those of not even that we
no lo de Agatha lo de Agatha han los de
were they made Agatha sit
ni que fuéramos han hecho que Agatha se
down on Friday in Friday because
siente el viernes en de viernes porque
it's giving a hype to a phrase that was
es dar un bombo a una frase que se
wrong but it's that we've been with
equivocó pero es que llevamos s días con
that phrase for days please I mean totally
esa frase por favor O sea totalmente
but one thing she has asked for forgiveness but
pero una cosa ha pedido perdón pero
because it has been seen because of the
porque se ha visto por la presión
public pressure and at the image level but knowing
pública y a nivel imagen pero conociendo
Agatha a little that I do have the
un poco a Agatha que yo sí que la tenid
wait Yes I have had to
espera Sí yo la he tenido que
interview her a thousand times Because she also
entrevistar mil veces Porque además
worked at the newspaper of  her ex-husband
trabajaba en el periódico de su exmarido
when that and I've interviewed her a
cuando aquello y la he entrevistado un
million times and knowing her a
millón de veces y conociéndola un
little bit it's been a bit of an
poquito ha sido un poco limpiecita de
image cleanup for her. She still thinks that it's the
imagen ella Sigue pensando que es la
typical phrase that I've also said
típica frase que yo también lo he dicho
here that it's the typical phrase that's been said all my
aquí que es la típica frase de toda la
life that I've also said a
vida hecha que yo también la he dicho un
million times when I was 13 14 years old there
millón de veces cuando tenía 13 14 años
are four five more and that the
es hay cuatro cinco más y que de la
phrase that they are not well but that they are in
frase que no están bien pero que son in
obviously that phrase should not be
obviamente esa frase no se tiene que
said under any circumstances at this point I understand that before we had a different mentality and we said a lot of phrases like that just like Regarding gays regarding I don't know what and we've learned and I think that phrase is a huge mistake that even the presenter should have realized at the time that I know
la presentadora en el momento que seijo
because I understand that there are people who
porque entiendo que haya gente que se
feel uh bad it's that I understand it as if
sienta eh mal es que lo entiendo como si
journalists are [ __ ]
di las periodistas son unas guarras
imagine Well as a journalist I
imagínate Pues yo como periodista me
feel bad then but I but I think
siento mal entonces pero yo pero creo
that Agatha from what I've been
que Agatha por lo que a mí me han
told is a real classist and I think
contado es una clasista de verdad y creo
she's a real racist because I
que es una racista de verdad porque
have people who have  informed
tengo a personas que me han informado
about her and they told me that
sobre ella y me han contado que es que
she is like that Another thing is that phrase
ella es así Otra cosa es que esa frase
but Marta It's like if I told you don't act like a
pero Marta Es como si yo te digo no te
Swede the same H it's the same no no no
hagas la sueca lo mismo H es lo mismo
no let's see let me talk eh it's
no no no no a ver me dejáis hablar eh es
like you have everything like a camp This
como tenéis todo como un campamento Esto
is like a gypsy camp don't act like a
está como un campamento de gitano no
Swede eh you have worked with a
tengas la sueca eh has trabajado con una
black woman they are expressions that are
negra son expresiones que está son
expressions that are wrong and Ah you have
expresiones que están mal y Ah tenéis
there in the chat you have there in the chat a
ahí en el chat tenéis ahí en el chat un
partner Edu is street there in the ch
compañero Está Edu calle ahí en el ch
Edu Edu a huge kiss kiss Edu that yes that is
Edu Edu un besito enorme beso Edu que sí
strong that the thing about Agath is that she
que fuerte que es que lo de agath es que
is a real one is that I think that yes
es una de verdad es que yo creo que sí
in her case Yes in her case Yes I mean in her
en su caso Sí en su caso Sí o sea en su
case I like this whole plot It's that
caso me gusta de toda esta trama Es que
then a jerk gets involved and screws up more
luego patón se meta y la cague más
then that's how it always happens that this is the
entonces eso es como siempre pasa que es
plan this poor lawyer of mine
plan este este señor abogado pobre mío
at what moment did he decide to defend his
en qué momento decidió defender a su
wife his girlfriend by bringing in the other one or I
mujer a su novia metiendo a la otra o
mean it's something like and then everyone
sea es algo como y luego todo el mundo
reacting I loved the reaction
reaccionando Me encantó la reacción
Well pitingo I mean everything is that it's like
Bueno pitingo o sea todo es que es como
a plot that  creates a plot from a phrase
una trama que se crea de una frase una
then the other goes the one from Friday
trama luego la otra va el de viernes
then it is that it is really that Lu But
luego es que de verdad es que Lu Pero
this also makes you see the lack of
esto también te hace ver la falta de
content that we have really clear eh we
contenido que tenemos realmente claro eh
were talking about it here we were
lo estuvimos hablando aquí lo estuvimos
talking about it here totally But that for the
hablando aquí total to Pero eso por el
sálvame or rather for me I that they will remove
sálvame o sea yo para mí yo que quitarán
the sálvame is that not only do
el sálvame es que ya no solamente que
we lack content for the sálvame is
nos falte contenido por el sálvame es
that the sálvame was like the nucleus of
que el sálvame era como el núcleo de
everything and from there
todo y ya de ahí como que se alimentaban
all the programs were fed even from the
todos los programas incluso de la
producer an Rosa creates a
productora an Rosa crea se creaba un
content was created and also you now think that
contenido y además tú ahora piensa que
all the people who participate in Salva
toda la gente que participa en Salva
are vetoed with which those people
está vetada con lo cual ellas personas
that before we spoke every day in
que antes hablábamos todos los días en
Ana rosaas It is that plots of Matamoros
Ana rosaas Es que tramas de Matamoros
Ben this
Ben este
Chelo Bárbara is that they were things that we
Chelo Bárbara es que eran cosas que
were dealing with every day at that
estábamos tratando cada día en ese
moment they have removed all the topics in one fell swoop
momento han quitado de un plumazo todos
So what is left,
los temas Entonces qué se queda no se
nothing is left, nothing is left
queda nada no queda nada
[Music]
[Música]